Adebowale Oduwole

Atlanta, GA (470)-285-4205 aoduwole7@gmail.com

Software Developer with 5+ years of combined experience in Web Dev & IT, currently enrolled in Accelerate Atlantas Azure Fundamentals program. Also Pursuing a B.S. in Organisational Leadership at Point University in Atlanta, GA. Seeking to expand my knowledge and experience through an IT apprenticeship role with Google.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Microsoft's Azure Fundamentals Certification (AZ-900)
- Comptia Information Technology Fundamentals (ITF+)

EDUCATION

POINT UNIVERSITY, ATLANTA, GA

• Completed 60 of 120 required credit hours required for BS in Organizational Leadership

WORK EXPERIENCE

United Parcel Service, Atlanta, GA *Package Handler, March 2019 – October 2019*

- Double Checked and Loaded/Unloaded packages
- Inspected parcels for damage, leaks, etc.
- Operated mechanical equipment to ensure each package reached it's proper destination.

CHICK-FIL-A, FAYETTEVILLE, GA & HAPEVILLE, GA Cook, March 2018 – August 2018

- Prepared menu items according to quality standards, managing several cooking stations at a time.
- Managed Storage & Handling of food product, adhering to Chick-Fil-A's established food safety, handling, and sanitation procedures.

Crew. March 2016 – November 2016

- Managed deliveries & inventory, followed proper record documentation and food handling procedures and ensured that any inventory issues are corrected.
- Worked to maintain clean customer facing areas both in and out of the restaurant.
- Helped train new employees to properly execute job duties to the standards set by the company.
- Resolved customer grievances & when necessary escalate issues to management.